var data = [
	{"answer":"12 Years A Slave","question":"In the antebellum United States, Solomon Northup, a free black man from upstate New York, is abducted and sold into slavery."},
	{"answer":"The Sound of Music","question":"A woman leaves an Austrian convent to become a governess to the children of a Naval officer widower."},
	{"answer":"The Sting","question":"In Chicago in September 1936, a young con man seeking revenge for his murdered partner teams up with a master of the big con to win a fortune from a criminal banker."},
	{"answer":"Gladiator","question":"When a Roman general is betrayed and his family murdered by an emperor's corrupt son, he comes to Rome mutto seek revenge."},
	{"answer":"Grand Hotel","question":"A group of very different individuals staying at a luxurious hotel in Berlin deal with each of their respective dramas."},
	{"answer":"All About Eve","question":"An ingenue insinuates herself into the company of an established but aging stage actress and her circle of theater friends."},
	{"answer":"It Happened One Night","question":"A spoiled heiress, running away from her family, is helped by a man who is actually a reporter in need of a story."},
	{"answer":"Titanic","question":"A seventeen-year-old aristocrat falls in love with a kind, but poor artist on an ill-fated journey."},
	{"answer":"Birdman or (The Unexpected Virtue of Ignorance)","question":"Illustrated upon the progress of his latest Broadway play, a former popular actor's struggle to cope with his current life as a wasted actor."},
	{"answer":"Braveheart","question":"When his secret bride is executed for assaulting an English soldier who tried to rape her, a knight begins a revolt and leads Scottish warriors against the cruel English tyrant who rules Scotland with an iron fist."},
	{"answer":"The Deer Hunter","question":"An in-depth examination of the ways in which the U.S. Vietnam war impacts and disrupts the lives of people in a small industrial town in Pennsylvania."},
	{"answer":"Mutiny on the Bounty","question":"A sailor successfully leads a revolt against his ruthless ship captain. The captain returns one year later, hell bent on avenging his captors."},
	{"answer":"Kramer vs. Kramer","question":"A man rediscovers his bond with his son after his wife leaves him, but a custody battle over the child deepens the wounds left by separation"},
	{"answer":"The Great Ziegfeld","question":"The ups and downs of Florenz Ziegfeld, famed producer of extravagant stage revues."},
	{"answer":"Gandhi","question":"The life of the lawyer who became the famed leader of the Indian revolt against the British rule through his philosophy of nonviolent protest."},
	{"answer":"Midnight Cowboy","question":"A naive hustler goes to New York to seek personal fortune, but in the process finds himself a new friend."},
	{"answer":"Hamlet","question":"A Danish prince struggles over whether or not he should kill his uncle, whom he suspects has murdered his father, the former king."},
	{"answer":"How Green Was My Valley","question":"At the turn of the century in a Welsh mining village, a family raises coal-mining sons and hope their youngest will find a better life."},
	{"answer":"The Apartment","question":"A man tries to rise in his company by letting its executives use his apartment for trysts, but complications and a romance of his own ensue."},
	{"answer":"The Godfather 2","question":"The early life and career of a gangster in 1920s New York is portrayed while his son expands and tightens his grip on his crime syndicate"},
	{"answer":"The Bridge on the River Kwai","question":"After settling his differences with a Japanese PoW camp commander, a British colonel co-operates to oversee his men's construction of a railway bridge for their captors - while oblivious to a plan by the Allies to destroy it."},
	{"answer":"In the Heat of the Night","question":"An African American police detective is asked to investigate a murder in a racially hostile southern town."},
	{"answer":"Going My Way","question":"A youthful Father who has led a colorful life of sports, song, and romance before joining the Roman Catholic clergy, is met with skepticism. But he inspires the youth of his parish and transform it completely"},
	{"answer":"American Beauty","question":"A sexually frustrated suburban father has a mid-life crisis after becoming infatuated with his daughter's best friend."},
	{"answer":"Casablanca","question":"During the early days of World War II, an American expatriate meets a former lover, with unforeseen complications."},
	{"answer":"You Can't Take It with You","question":"A man from a family of rich snobs becomes engaged to a woman from a good-natured, but decidedly eccentric, family."},
	{"answer":"The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King","question":"A wizard and a king lead an army against an evil lord's army to draw his gaze from the plot to destroy his source of power."},
	{"answer":"The Last Emperor","question":"The story of the final Emperor of China."},
	{"answer":"Lawrence of Arabia","question":"A brilliant, flamboyant, and controversial British military figure and his conflicted loyalties during wartime service."},
	{"answer":"The Godfather","question":"The aging patriarch of an organized crime dynasty transfers control of his clandestine empire to his reluctant son."},
	{"answer":"West Side Story","question":"Two youngsters from rival New York City gangs fall in love, but tensions between their respective friends build toward tragedy."},
	{"answer":"The Artist","question":"A silent movie star meets a young dancer, but the arrival of talking pictures sends their careers in opposite directions."},
	{"answer":"The English Patient","question":"At the close of WWII, a young nurse tends to a badly-burned plane crash victim. His past is shown in flashbacks, revealing an involvement in a fateful love affair."},
	{"answer":"Rocky","question":"A small-time boxer gets a supremely rare chance to fight the heavy-weight champion in a bout in which he strives to go the distance for his self-respect."},
	{"answer":"Annie Hall","question":"A neurotic New York comedian falls in love with a ditsy girl."},
	{"answer":"Gone with the Wind","question":"A manipulative Southern belle carries on a turbulent affair with a blockade runner during the American Civil War."},
	{"answer":"Rebecca","question":"A self-conscious bride is tormented by the memory of her husband's dead first wife."},
	{"answer":"Chariots of Fire","question":"Two British track athletes, one a determined Jew and the other a devout Christian, compete in the 1924 Olympics."},
	{"answer":"Gentleman's Agreement","question":"A reporter pretends to be Jewish in order to cover a story on anti-Semitism, and personally discovers the true depths of bigotry and hatred."},
	{"answer":"Around the World in 80 Days","question":"A Victorian Englishman who bets that with the new steamships and railways he can help him win a bet"},
	{"answer":"Mrs. Miniver","question":"A British family struggles to survive the first months of World War II."},
	{"answer":"On the Waterfront","question":"An ex-prize fighter turned longshoreman struggles to stand up to his corrupt union bosses."},
	{"answer":"Dances With Wolves","question":"Exiled to a remote western Civil War outpost, a lieutenant befriends wolves and Indians, making him an intolerable aberration in the military."},
	{"answer":"Chicago","question":"Two murderesses find themselves on death row together and fight for the fame that will keep them from the gallows in 1920s Chicago."},
	{"answer":"The Silence of the Lambs","question":"A young F.B.I. cadet must confide in an incarcerated and manipulative killer to receive his help on catching another serial killer"},
	{"answer":"The Departed","question":"An undercover cop and a mole in the police attempt to identify each other while infiltrating an Irish gang in South Boston."},
	{"answer":"Cavalcade","question":"A cavalcade of English life from New Year's Eve 1899 until 1933 seen through the eyes of well-to-do Londoners Jane and Robert Marryot"},
	{"answer":"Cimarron","question":"A newspaper editor settles in an Oklahoma boom town with his reluctant wife at the end of the nineteenth century."},
	{"answer":"Out of Africa","question":"In 20th-century colonial Kenya, a Danish baroness/plantation owner has a passionate love affair with a free-spirited big-game hunter."},
	{"answer":"The Hurt Locker","question":"During the Iraq War, a Sergeant recently assigned to an army bomb squad is put at odds with his squad mates due to his maverick way of handling his work."},
	{"answer":"Platoon","question":"A young recruit in Vietnam faces a moral crisis when confronted with the horrors of war and the duality of man."},
	{"answer":"Shakespeare in Love","question":"A young Shakespeare, out of ideas and short of cash, meets his ideal woman and is inspired to write one of his most famous plays."},
	{"answer":"Schindler's List","question":"In Poland during World War II, a businessman gradually becomes concerned for his Jewish workforce after witnessing their persecution by the Nazis."},
	{"answer":"Terms of Endearment","question":"Follows hard-to-please Aurora looking for love and her daughter's family problems."},
	{"answer":"Patton","question":"The World War II phase of the career of a controversial American general"},
	{"answer":"The Best Years of Our Lives","question":"Three WWII veterans return home to small-town America to discover that they and their families have been irreparably changed."},
	{"answer":"Crash","question":"Los Angeles citizens with vastly separate lives collide in interweaving stories of race, loss and redemption."},
	{"answer":"All Quiet on the Western Front","question":"A young soldier faces profound disillusionment in the soul-destroying horror of World War I."},
	{"answer":"Ben-Hur","question":"When a Jewish prince is betrayed and sent into slavery by a Roman friend, he regains his freedom and comes back for revenge."},
	{"answer":"Slumdog Millionaire","question":"A Mumbai teen reflects on his upbringing in the slums when he is accused of cheating on the Indian Version of "},
	{"answer":"The King's Speech","question":"The story of King George VI of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, his impromptu ascension to the throne and the speech therapist who helped the unsure monarch become worthy of it."},
	{"answer":"Gigi","question":"Weary of the conventions of Parisian society, a rich playboy and a youthful courtesan-in-training enjoy a platonic friendship, but it may not stay platonic for long."},
	{"answer":"An American in Paris","question":"Three friends struggle to find work in Paris. However, things become more complicated when two of them fall in love with the same woman."},
	{"answer":"Driving Miss Daisy","question":"An old Jewish woman and her African-American chauffeur in the American South have a relationship that grows and improves over the years."},
	{"answer":"Million Dollar Baby","question":"A determined woman works with a hardened boxing trainer to become a professional."},
	{"answer":"Wings","question":"Two young men, one rich, one middle class, who are in love with the same woman, become fighter pilots in World War I."},
	{"answer":"Rain Man","question":"A selfish yuppie discovers his father has left a fortune to his savant brother and a pittance to him; the duo travel cross-country"},
	{"answer":"The French Connection","question":"A pair of NYC cops in the Narcotics Bureau stumble onto a drug smuggling job with a French connection."},
	{"answer":"One Flew over the Cuckoo's Nest","question":"A criminal pleads insanity after getting into trouble again and once in the mental institution, rebels against the oppressive nurse and rallies up the scared patients."},
	{"answer":"Oliver!","question":"Musical adaptation about an orphan who runs away from an orphanage and hooks up with a group of boys trained to be pickpockets by an elderly mentor."},
	{"answer":"Marty","question":"A middle-aged butcher and a school teacher who have given up on the idea of love, meet at a dance and fall in love."},
	{"answer":"The Broadway Melody","question":"Harriet and Queenie Mahoney, a vaudeville act, come to Broadway, where their friend Eddie Kerns invites his girlfriend Hank to join him."},
	{"answer":"All the Kings Men","question":"The rise and fall of a corrupt politician, who makes his friends richer and retains power by dint of a populist appeal."},
	{"answer":"A Man for All Seasons","question":"The story of Thomas More, who stood up to King Henry VIII when the King rejected the Roman Catholic Church to obtain a divorce and remarriage."},
	{"answer":"The Lost Weekend","question":"The desperate life of a chronic alcoholic is followed through a four day drinking bout."},
	{"answer":"Tom Jones","question":"In eighteenth century England, first cousins grow up together in privilege in the countryside but couldn't be more different."},
	{"answer":"From Here to Eternity","question":"In 1941 Hawaii, a private is cruelly punished for not boxing on his unit's team, while his captain's wife and second in command are falling in love."},
	{"answer":"Amadeus","question":"The incredible story of a legendary musician, told by his peer and secret rival - now confined to an insane asylum."},
	{"answer":"No Country for Old Men","question":"Violence and mayhem ensue after a hunter stumbles upon a drug deal gone wrong and more than two million dollars in cash near the Rio Grande."},
	{"answer":"The Greatest Show on Earth","question":"The dramatic lives of trapeze artists, a clown, and an elephant trainer against a background of circus spectacle."},
	{"answer":"Unforgiven","question":"A retired Old West gunslinger reluctantly takes on one last job, with the help of his old partner and a young man."},
	{"answer":"Forrest Gump","question":"A seemingly unintelligent man has accidentally been present at many historic moments, but his true love eludes him."},
	{"answer":"My Fair Lady","question":"A misogynistic and snobbish phonetics professor agrees to a wager that he can take a flower girl and make her presentable in high society."},
	{"answer":"A Beautiful Mind","question":"After a brilliant but asocial mathematician accepts secret work in cryptography, his life takes a turn for the nightmarish."},
	{"answer":"Argo","question":"Acting under the cover of a Hollywood producer scouting a location for a science fiction film, a CIA agent launches a dangerous operation to rescue six Americans in Tehran during the U.S. hostage crisis in Iran in 1980."},
	{"answer":"The Life of Emile Zola","question":"The biopic of the famous French muckraking writer and his involvement in fighting the injustice of the Dreyfuss Affair."},
	{"answer":"Ordinary People","question":"The accidental death of the older son of an affluent family deeply strains the relationships among the bitter mother, the good-natured father, and the guilt-ridden younger son."}
];

var choices = ['Birdman or (The Unexpected Virtue of Ignorance)', 'American Sniper', 'Boyhood', 'The Imitation Game', 'The Grand Budapest Hotel', 'Selma', 'The Theory of Everything', 'Whiplash', '12 Years a Slave', 'American Hustle', 'Captain Phillips', 'Dallas Buyers Club', 'Gravity', 'Her', 'Nebraska', 'Philomena', 'The Wolf of Wall Street', 'Argo', 'Beasts of the Southern Wild', 'Zero Dark Thirty', 'Amour', 'Silver Linings Playbook', 'Lincoln', 'Life of Pi', 'Les Miserables', 'Django Unchained', 'The Artist', 'The Tree of Life', 'The Descendants', 'Extremely Loud & Incredibly Close', 'The Help', 'Hugo', 'Midnight in Paris', 'Moneyball', 'War Horse', "The King's Speech", '127 Hours', 'Black Swan', 'The Fighter', 'Inception', 'The Kids Are All Right', 'The Social Network', 'Toy Story 3', 'True Grit', 'The Hurt Locker', 'A Serious Man', 'An Education', 'Avatar', 'District 9', 'Inglourious Basterds', 'Precious', 'The Blind Side', 'Up', 'Up in the Air', 'Slumdog Millionaire', 'The Curious Case of Benjamin Button', 'Frost/Nixon', 'Milk', 'The Reader', 'No Country for Old Men', 'Atonement', 'Juno', 'Michael Clayton', 'There Will Be Blood', 'The Departed', 'Babel', 'Letters from Iwo Jima', 'Little Miss Sunshine', 'The Queen', 'Crash', 'Brokeback Mountain', 'Capote', 'Good Night, and Good Luck.', 'Munich', 'Million Dollar Baby', 'The Aviator', 'Finding Neverland', 'Ray', 'Sideways', 'The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King', 'Lost in Translation', 'Master and Commander: The Far Side of the World', 'Mystic River', 'Seabiscuit', 'Chicago', 'Gangs of New York', 'The Hours', 'The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers', 'The Pianist', 'A Beautiful Mind', 'Gosford Park', 'In the Bedroom', 'The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring', 'Moulin Rouge!', 'Gladiator', 'Chocolat', 'Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon', 'Erin Brockovich', 'Traffic', 'American Beauty', 'The Cider House Rules', 'The Green Mile', 'The Insider', 'The Sixth Sense', 'Shakespeare in Love', 'Elizabeth', 'Life Is Beautiful', 'Saving Private Ryan', 'The Thin Red Line', 'Titanic', 'As Good as It Gets', 'The Full Monty', 'Good Will Hunting', 'L.A. Confidential', 'The English Patient', 'Fargo', 'Jerry Maguire', 'Secrets & Lies', 'Shine', 'Braveheart', 'Apollo 13', 'Babe', 'Il Postino: The Postman', 'Sense and Sensibility', 'Forrest Gump', 'Four Weddings and a Funeral', 'Pulp Fiction', 'Quiz Show', 'The Shawshank Redemption', "Schindler's List", 'The Fugitive', 'In the Name of the Father', 'The Piano', 'The Remains of the Day', 'Unforgiven', 'The Crying Game', 'A Few Good Men', 'Howards End', 'Scent of a Woman', 'The Silence of the Lambs', 'Beauty and the Beast', 'Bugsy', 'JFK', 'The Prince of Tides', 'Dances with Wolves', 'Awakenings', 'Ghost', 'The Godfather: Part III', 'Goodfellas', 'Driving Miss Daisy', 'Born on the Fourth of July', 'Dead Poets Society', 'Field of Dreams', 'My Left Foot', 'Rain Man', 'The Accidental Tourist', 'Dangerous Liaisons', 'Mississippi Burning', 'Working Girl', 'The Last Emperor', 'Broadcast News', 'Fatal Attraction', 'Hope and Glory', 'Moonstruck', 'Platoon', 'Children of a Lesser God', 'Hannah and Her Sisters', 'The Mission', 'A Room with a View', 'Out of Africa', 'The Color Purple', 'Kiss of the Spider Woman', "Prizzi's Honor", 'Witness', 'Amadeus', 'The Killing Fields', 'A Passage to India', 'Places in the Heart', "A Soldier's Story", 'Terms of Endearment', 'The Big Chill', 'The Dresser', 'The Right Stuff', 'Tender Mercies', 'Gandhi', 'E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial', 'Missing', 'Tootsie', 'The Verdict', 'Chariots of Fire', 'Atlantic City', 'On Golden Pond', 'Raiders of the Lost Ark', 'Reds', 'Ordinary People', "Coal Miner's Daughter", 'The Elephant Man', 'Raging Bull', 'Tess', 'Kramer vs. Kramer', 'All That Jazz', 'Apocalypse Now', 'Breaking Away', 'Norma Rae', 'The Deer Hunter', 'Coming Home', 'Heaven Can Wait', 'Midnight Express', 'An Unmarried Woman', 'Annie Hall', 'The Goodbye Girl', 'Julia', 'Star Wars', 'The Turning Point', 'Rocky', "All the President's Men", 'Bound for Glory', 'Network', 'Taxi Driver', "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest", 'Barry Lyndon', 'Dog Day Afternoon', 'Jaws', 'Nashville', 'The Godfather: Part II', 'Chinatown', 'The Conversation', 'Lenny', 'The Towering Inferno', 'The Sting', 'American Graffiti', 'Cries & Whispers', 'The Exorcist', 'A Touch of Class', 'The Godfather', 'Cabaret', 'Deliverance', 'The Emigrants', 'Sounder', 'The French Connection', 'A Clockwork Orange', 'Fiddler on the Roof', 'The Last Picture Show', 'Nicholas and Alexandra', 'Patton', 'Airport', 'Five Easy Pieces', 'Love Story', 'MASH', 'Midnight Cowboy', 'Anne of the Thousand Days', 'Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid', 'Hello, Dolly!', 'Z', 'Oliver!', 'Funny Girl', 'The Lion in Winter', 'Rachel, Rachel', 'Romeo and Juliet', 'In the Heat of the Night', 'Bonnie and Clyde', 'Doctor Dolittle', 'The Graduate', "Guess Who's Coming to Dinner", 'A Man for All Seasons', 'Alfie', 'The Russians Are Coming the Russians Are Coming', 'The Sand Pebbles', "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?", 'The Sound of Music', 'Darling', 'Doctor Zhivago', 'Ship of Fools', 'A Thousand Clowns', 'My Fair Lady', 'Becket', 'Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb', 'Mary Poppins', 'Zorba the Greek', 'Tom Jones', 'America America', 'Cleopatra', 'How the West Was Won', 'Lilies of the Field', 'Lawrence of Arabia', 'The Longest Day', 'The Music Man', 'Mutiny on the Bounty', 'To Kill a Mockingbird', 'West Side Story', 'Fanny', 'The Guns of Navarone', 'The Hustler', 'Judgment at Nuremberg', 'The Apartment', 'The Alamo', 'Elmer Gantry', 'Sons and Lovers', 'The Sundowners', 'Ben-Hur', 'Anatomy of a Murder', 'The Diary of Anne Frank', "The Nun's Story", 'Room at the Top', 'Gigi', 'Auntie Mame', 'Cat on a Hot Tin Roof', 'The Defiant Ones', 'Separate Tables', 'The Bridge on the River Kwai', 'Peyton Place', 'Sayonara', '12 Angry Men', 'Witness for the Prosecution', 'Around the World in 80 Days', 'Friendly Persuasion', 'Giant', 'The King and I', 'The Ten Commandments', 'Marty', 'Love Is a Many-Splendored Thing', 'Mister Roberts', 'Picnic', 'The Rose Tattoo', 'On the Waterfront', 'The Caine Mutiny', 'The Country Girl', 'Seven Brides for Seven Brothers', 'Three Coins in the Fountain', 'From Here to Eternity', 'Julius Caesar', 'The Robe', 'Roman Holiday', 'Shane', 'The Greatest Show on Earth', 'High Noon', 'Ivanhoe', 'Moulin Rouge', 'The Quiet Man', 'An American in Paris', 'Decision Before Dawn', 'A Place in the Sun', 'Quo Vadis', 'A Streetcar Named Desire', 'All About Eve', 'Born Yesterday', 'Father of the Bride', "King Solomon's Mines", 'Sunset Blvd.', "All the King's Men", 'Battleground', 'The Heiress', 'A Letter to Three Wives', "Twelve O'Clock High", 'Hamlet', 'Johnny Belinda', 'The Red Shoes', 'The Snake Pit', 'The Treasure of the Sierra Madre', "Gentleman's Agreement", "The Bishop's Wife", 'Crossfire', 'Great Expectations', 'Miracle on 34th Street', 'The Best Years of Our Lives', 'Henry V', "It's a Wonderful Life", "The Razor's Edge", 'The Yearling', 'The Lost Weekend', 'Anchors Aweigh', "The Bells of St. Mary's", 'Mildred Pierce', 'Spellbound', 'Going My Way', 'Double Indemnity', 'Gaslight', 'Since You Went Away', 'Wilson', 'Casablanca', 'For Whom the Bell Tolls', 'Heaven Can Wait', 'The Human Comedy', 'In Which We Serve', 'Madame Curie', 'The More the Merrier', 'The Ox-Bow Incident', 'The Song of Bernadette', 'Watch on the Rhine', 'Mrs. Miniver', '49th Parallel', 'Kings Row', 'The Magnificent Ambersons', 'The Pied Piper', 'The Pride of the Yankees', 'Random Harvest', 'The Talk of the Town', 'Wake Island', 'Yankee Doodle Dandy', 'How Green Was My Valley', 'Blossoms in the Dust', 'Citizen Kane', 'Here Comes Mr. Jordan', 'Hold Back the Dawn', 'The Little Foxes', 'The Maltese Falcon', 'One Foot in Heaven', 'Sergeant York', 'Suspicion', 'Rebecca', 'All This, and Heaven Too', 'Foreign Correspondent', 'The Grapes of Wrath', 'The Great Dictator', 'Kitty Foyle', 'The Letter', 'The Long Voyage Home', 'Our Town', 'The Philadelphia Story', 'Gone with the Wind', 'Dark Victory', 'Goodbye, Mr. Chips', 'Love Affair', 'Mr. Smith Goes to Washington', 'Ninotchka', 'Of Mice and Men', 'Stagecoach', 'The Wizard of Oz', 'Wuthering Heights', "You Can't Take It With You", 'The Adventures of Robin Hood', "Alexander's Ragtime Band", 'Boys Town', 'The Citadel', 'Four Daughters', 'Grand Illusion', 'Jezebel', 'Pygmalion', 'Test Pilot', 'The Life of Emile Zola', 'The Awful Truth', 'Captains Courageous', 'Dead End', 'The Good Earth', 'In Old Chicago', 'Lost Horizon', 'One Hundred Men and a Girl', 'Stage Door', 'A Star Is Born', 'The Great Ziegfeld', 'Anthony Adverse', 'Dodsworth', 'Libeled Lady', 'Mr. Deeds Goes to Town', 'Romeo and Juliet', 'San Francisco', 'The Story of Louis Pasteur', 'A Tale of Two Cities', 'Three Smart Girls', 'Mutiny on the Bounty', 'Alice Adams', 'Broadway Melody of 1936', 'Captain Blood\xc3\x8a[J]', 'David Copperfield', 'The Informer\xc3\x8a[J]', 'The Lives of a Bengal Lancer', "A Midsummer Night's Dream", 'Les Miserables', 'Naughty Marietta', 'Ruggles of Red Gap', 'Top Hat', 'It Happened One Night', 'The Barretts of Wimpole Street', 'Cleopatra', 'Flirtation Walk', 'The Gay Divorcee', 'Here Comes the Navy', 'The House of Rothschild', 'Imitation of Life', 'One Night of Love', 'The Thin Man', 'Viva Villa!', 'The White Parade', 'Cavalcade', '42nd Street', 'A Farewell to Arms', 'I Am a Fugitive from a Chain Gang', 'Lady for a Day', 'Little Women', 'The Private Life of Henry VIII', 'She Done Him Wrong', "Smilin' Through", 'State Fair', 'Grand Hotel', 'Arrowsmith', 'Bad Girl', 'The Champ', 'Five Star Final', 'One Hour with You', 'Shanghai Express', 'The Smiling Lieutenant', 'Cimarron', 'East Lynne', 'The Front Page', 'Skippy', 'Trader Horn', 'All Quiet on the Western Front', 'The Big House', 'Disraeli', 'The Divorcee', 'The Love Parade', 'The Broadway Melody', 'Alibi', 'Hollywood Revue', 'In Old Arizona', 'The Patriot', 'Wings', 'The Racket', 'Seventh Heaven'];


var last = 'http://49.media.tumblr.com/ede62d117e26ffe702af74dbd48213c4/tumblr_n13zic8aQK1sztll3o1_400.gif';

var leoGifs = ['http://49.media.tumblr.com/2c5090eb4a9755a78f5f7052f4046024/tumblr_n8o1rgjN8P1ttghbto8_250.gif',
				'http://45.media.tumblr.com/d345a00017dcc3f68784635ccc036359/tumblr_mus1evczrq1spk3foo1_250.gif',
				'http://45.media.tumblr.com/9c1b50e0db5858d4288f92438d92352b/tumblr_n7dwtrql961rl33l5o1_500.gif',
				'http://45.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m2u8extdTi1r3wk77o2_500.gif',
				'http://38.media.tumblr.com/4a2d68f177f9651373c04fe845c44907/tumblr_n8hnl56dlS1sfoav0o1_500.gif',
				'http://38.media.tumblr.com/7c8b1209a4ae493443cdf2266094220c/tumblr_nlhlhdP2Od1u9x7l6o1_500.gif',
				'http://37.media.tumblr.com/4efe2667ea34d0b44ecb121b1f708f5c/tumblr_nawh2oKNwN1tiorito1_500.gif',
				'http://24.media.tumblr.com/01bd89810d8df0f42dd7b683d50729ff/tumblr_n2ypoxqbFu1s9ab4to1_500.gif',
				'http://25.media.tumblr.com/8fdbbcb240cc7461f290530c7aeaf336/tumblr_n0x034Xz6S1sk81sjo1_250.gif',
				'http://37.media.tumblr.com/5b976bd3c93a46553b0c0f33dff53727/tumblr_n29g26VpiJ1rijbg1o1_500.gif',
				'http://49.media.tumblr.com/a805797b4068a370e8f6ac76be7b78c1/tumblr_o0rsoau26e1r1q21qo1_500.gif',
				'http://24.media.tumblr.com/46ba7bf410ba410dc7b57b33e5bcf32c/tumblr_n023f2QFVF1r97o1mo1_500.gif',
				'http://24.media.tumblr.com/fee3cd65beefd70d020dc466c9f5c39e/tumblr_mygzhr0o1j1r3fkfio1_500.gif',
				'http://38.media.tumblr.com/e2e6c916bbeadda65af3209bca88405d/tumblr_nsiyuy6XgN1ruqjbeo1_400.gif',
				'http://37.media.tumblr.com/39258af9ee50deced76f915cd0dd8c42/tumblr_n3ckbaBQLO1sfoav0o1_500.gif',
				'http://24.media.tumblr.com/215b219f4e556afc2ffb1408b0aa89be/tumblr_mkqmm5VsYE1qagmv6o1_500.gif',
				'http://25.media.tumblr.com/27f1d1b0a839c0bec08755002ef19a17/tumblr_mrqqk1tzyX1sx80b0o1_500.gif',
				'http://25.media.tumblr.com/797fac0ebcc33849fef2e2b365ed7985/tumblr_mn1zd0Ghjn1srtlkoo1_500.gif',
				'http://31.media.tumblr.com/ba7341a40fb23e1d4a1d3264849d4063/tumblr_msyc4uveWv1selx09o1_500.gif',
				'http://31.media.tumblr.com/dab134b948ab47dc597a5743ea73057e/tumblr_molhnnx0dB1r4q6qoo1_400.gif',
				'http://25.media.tumblr.com/30bf2cf14f7c96c28d44dbced23f03b4/tumblr_mm8lyq4Sa51qf5do9o1_400.gif',
				'http://31.media.tumblr.com/a7dbfacd366ab03cadafe1a8faa6a275/tumblr_meuue4EJAm1rd11tco1_1280.gif',
				'http://31.media.tumblr.com/a3e213403f4b45917cd365c783d9b894/tumblr_mqsefuP9q61r8q1s0o1_250.gif',
				'http://31.media.tumblr.com/1d379527df97681dd8b71ebf207c71d4/tumblr_mrvls9lnVk1rfm6lno1_500.gif',
				'http://25.media.tumblr.com/916e8ee5e2da790ebe5d3a79d7fb1d10/tumblr_mnqkytpqyS1so9fmco1_500.gif',
				];